import type { MCQ } from '../../../types'

export const mcqSet2: MCQ[] = [
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "What is another term for anomaly detection?",
    "options": [
      "Outlier detection",
      "Trend analysis",
      "Data normalization",
      "Signal processing"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "Which method measures the number of standard deviations a data point is from the mean?",
    "options": [
      "IQR",
      "Z-score",
      "KNN",
      "DBSCAN"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "Which of the following is an example of a simple text prediction application?",
    "options": [
      "Speech-to-text transcription",
      "Image captioning",
      "Autocomplete in search engines",
      "Sentiment analysis"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "A higher BLEU score in text prediction indicates:",
    "options": [
      "Better performance",
      "Worse performance",
      "No change in performance",
      "The model is overfitting"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT a type of recommender system?",
    "options": [
      "Content-based filtering",
      "Collaborative filtering",
      "User-based filtering",
      "Deep filtering"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "Which application area is NOT typically associated with recommender systems?",
    "options": [
      "E-commerce",
      "Weather forecasting",
      "Streaming services",
      "Social media"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "Which of the following types of collaborative filtering uses machine learning algorithms to build a model on the user-item rating dataset?",
    "options": [
      "Memory-Based CF",
      "User-Based CF",
      "Model-Based CF",
      "Item-Based CF"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "Which similarity measure calculates the straight-line distance between two users' preference vectors?",
    "options": [
      "Cosine Similarity",
      "Pearson Correlation",
      "Euclidean Distance",
      "Jaccard Similarity"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "Which of the following is a component of Non-Negative Matrix Factorization?",
    "options": [
      "Mean Matrix",
      "Coefficient Matrix",
      "Diagonal Matrix",
      "Singular Matrix"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "What is a Non-Negative Matrix (NNM)?",
    "options": [
      "A matrix with all entries greater than zero",
      "A matrix with all entries less than zero",
      "A matrix with all entries non-negative",
      "A matrix with all entries equal to zero"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  }
]
